{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352946186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352946186"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352947262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352947262"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352949330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352949330"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352952347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352952347"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352955330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352955330"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352961936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352961936"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352964192","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352964192"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352968782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352968782"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352970739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352970739"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352974397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352974397"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352975466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352975466"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352976354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352976354"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352977047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352977047"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352981551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352981551"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352985688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352985688"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352989876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352989876"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_5v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352997284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352997284"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_5v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353016853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353016852"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 04c0afb5-8bda-4923-a727-4b77b4160003"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_5v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353016929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353016928"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 2dcb2349-e308-4a3f-b764-83952ea5cd16"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353027171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353027171"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 47b2c7e2-f397-4796-a937-801eaa644bbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_O-U-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353030951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353030950"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 47b2c7e2-f397-4796-a937-801eaa644bbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-O-E"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353037058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353037058"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 47b2c7e2-f397-4796-a937-801eaa644bbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-O-E"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353042241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353042241"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 47b2c7e2-f397-4796-a937-801eaa644bbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-O-E"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353047100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353047100"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 47b2c7e2-f397-4796-a937-801eaa644bbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-A-E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353052311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353052310"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 47b2c7e2-f397-4796-a937-801eaa644bbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-A-E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353056380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353056380"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 47b2c7e2-f397-4796-a937-801eaa644bbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_I-U-O"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353059693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353059692"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 47b2c7e2-f397-4796-a937-801eaa644bbf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_I-U-O"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353073373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353073373"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353075716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353075716"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353078460","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353078460"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353080401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353080401"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353084582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353084582"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353086770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353086770"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353091249","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353091249"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353094952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353094951"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353099559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353099559"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353104424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353104424"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353108972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353108972"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353113085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353113085"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353117299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353117298"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353119564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353119564"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353123668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353123668"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353125112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353125112"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_4v3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353134392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353134392"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_4v3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353141323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353141323"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_4v3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353147676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353147675"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 7953fd45-67eb-461a-8381-7e7a43cdb858"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_4v3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353157945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353157945"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" d651d383-b044-4c2a-8a8b-d9c9d0101f6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353163198","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353163198"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" d651d383-b044-4c2a-8a8b-d9c9d0101f6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353169102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353169102"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" d651d383-b044-4c2a-8a8b-d9c9d0101f6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353170454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353170454"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" d651d383-b044-4c2a-8a8b-d9c9d0101f6d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:vow.asc.A..Z.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353223846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353223845"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 90b11a9c-dad6-4aea-9437-df2700426741"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:vow.asc.A..Z.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353236653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353236652"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 90b11a9c-dad6-4aea-9437-df2700426741"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:vow.asc.A..Z.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353246400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353246400"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 90b11a9c-dad6-4aea-9437-df2700426741"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_I"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:vow.asc.A..Z.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353258573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353258573"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 90b11a9c-dad6-4aea-9437-df2700426741"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_O"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:vow.asc.A..Z.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353269150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353269150"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 90b11a9c-dad6-4aea-9437-df2700426741"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:vow.asc.A..Z.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353279287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353279282"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 90b11a9c-dad6-4aea-9437-df2700426741"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353288659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353288659"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 90b11a9c-dad6-4aea-9437-df2700426741"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353312521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353312521"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 90b11a9c-dad6-4aea-9437-df2700426741"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_vow.asc.A..Z.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353332164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353332164"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" f41585fe-017b-49f7-bd2c-343274cd3da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353341968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353341968"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" f41585fe-017b-49f7-bd2c-343274cd3da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353348423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353348422"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" f41585fe-017b-49f7-bd2c-343274cd3da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353354148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353354147"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" f41585fe-017b-49f7-bd2c-343274cd3da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353358568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353358567"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" f41585fe-017b-49f7-bd2c-343274cd3da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353370804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353370804"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 6c2930cb-2c22-4d8b-9fa1-3f3a65c44363"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-H-R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353375261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353375261"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 6c2930cb-2c22-4d8b-9fa1-3f3a65c44363"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-T-F"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353378861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353378861"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 6c2930cb-2c22-4d8b-9fa1-3f3a65c44363"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353383078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353383078"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 6c2930cb-2c22-4d8b-9fa1-3f3a65c44363"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-C-G"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353388390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353388390"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 6c2930cb-2c22-4d8b-9fa1-3f3a65c44363"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-C-G"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353393874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353393874"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 6c2930cb-2c22-4d8b-9fa1-3f3a65c44363"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-C-G"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353397779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353397779"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 6c2930cb-2c22-4d8b-9fa1-3f3a65c44363"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353403520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353403519"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 6c2930cb-2c22-4d8b-9fa1-3f3a65c44363"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353411784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353411783"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 6c2930cb-2c22-4d8b-9fa1-3f3a65c44363"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:vow.asc.A..Z.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353444190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353444190"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:vow.asc.A..Z.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353457534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353457534"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:vow.asc.A..Z.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353466204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353466204"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_I"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:vow.asc.A..Z.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353475907","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353475907"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_O"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:vow.asc.A..Z.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353477553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353477552"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_O"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:vow.asc.A..Z.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353482652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353482652"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_O"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:vow.asc.A..Z.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353493077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353493077"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:vow.asc.A..Z.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353506712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353506712"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:vow.asc.A..Z.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353509203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353509203"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:vow.asc.A..Z.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353515110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353515110"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:vow.asc.A..Z.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353518123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353518123"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:vow.asc.A..Z.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353524194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353524194"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:vow.asc.A..Z.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353533735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353533734"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353539704","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353539703"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353548859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353548859"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353557290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353557289"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353564274","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353564274"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353569070","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353569070"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:vow.asc.A..Z.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548353574826","data":{"timestamp":" 1548353574825"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_210201"," gameId":" 0513566b-854f-47af-adbd-fd03cb76e074"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_vow.asc.A..Z.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}